So I think, you know, we have a quite a broad effort to always think about this, but we don't
want to over-promise at this stage, sitting here in 2026, what may or may not happen five years
from now. But rest assured, those efforts are ongoing, and as soon as we have something that
we think is credible to put forward, we certainly will let the markets know.
Thank you. Your next question today comes from the line of Naresh Chohan from Intron Health.
Please go ahead. Hi there. Thanks for taking my question. Just one thing on carcinetics.
As we think about the margin impact of the carcinetics LOE,
is it fair to assume that you've already started optimizing the profitability of carcinetics
as would be typical ahead of any other LOE? Thank you. Thanks, Naresh. I'll give that to Mukul.
Yeah, Naresh, thanks for the question. Yeah, absolutely, I would confirm that. I think,
as we have previously indicated, I think we've projected an LOE in the U.S. for carcinetics in
2029. There is also an IRA event in 2020. So, I think, you know, we're going to have to
think about that in 2028 that we have factored into our numbers, and this is all baked into our
back to 40% latest by 2029 guidance in the margin. Thank you. Perfect. Thanks, Mukul.
Thank you. Your next question comes from the line of Seamus Fernandez from Guggenheim Securities.
Please go ahead. This is Zach Dunn on behalf of Seamus Fernandez. Thank you for the questions.
We're encouraged by...
the advancement of your IL-15, the GIA632 into vitiligo. Can you share your thoughts on how
you think about the market size of biologic eligible vitiligo patients? And if you don't
mind tying that into your thoughts on atopic dermatitis and the market opportunity there.
Thank you. Yeah, thanks. I mean, the IL-15 is something we did mention at the meet the
management, and we are quite excited by...
the profile of the...
over, you know, of this medicine. You know, for those of you who are not aware, this is a medicine that we in-license.
It's overexpressed in patients with atopic dermatitis, but we also see the opportunity to address a number of other,
you know, diseases over time, including, including vitiligo. And so it's early days. I mean, these phase two studies are ongoing.